http://www.banner-tribune.com/privacy-policy

Main menu
HomeAbout UsBlogsRSS FeedPrivacy PolicyUser AgreementAdvertiseNewsLocalStateObituariesPolice ReportsBusinessEditorialColumnsCOVID-19SportsHigh SchoolCollegeColumnsNFLOutdoorRacingLifestyleFormsGamesCrossword puzzleSudokuWeddingsBirthsColumnsLegalsFranklin Public NoticesMorgan City Public NoticesSearch Public NoticesMicrofilm archivesClassifiedsFranklin ClassifiedsMorgan City ClassifiedsArchivesFranklin Banner-Tribune Archivesdaily review archivesBayou Pioneer ArchivesSubscribe
Privacy Policy
What information does LouisianaStateNewspapers.com gather/track about you?LouisianaStateNewspapers.com has adopted a set of information management guidelines that serve as the basis for our customer and advertiser relationships. These guidelines have been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, guidelines are subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page. If the changes represent a material departure from our current practices with respect to the use of personal information, the changes will be posted on this page thirty days prior to taking effect and registered users will be notified via email.LouisianaStateNewspapers.com is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of Web sites to which it may link.
Registration: During a registration process LouisianaStateNewspapers.com asks that you supply a unique e-mail address, and demographic information (country, zip code, age, sex; household income, industry, job title, job function, and newspaper subscription status).
Contests, Special Offers and Other Promotions: On occasion, LouisianaStateNewspapers.com also collects additional personal information from subscribers in connection with optional contests, surveys, or special offers sometimes with unaffiliated third parties. Participants in these optional services agree to have their personal information shared with these parties. You may choose to not have your information shared by not participating in these offerings.
Cookies: LouisianaStateNewspapers.com employs cookies to recognize you and your access privileges on our web site, as well as to track site usage. Subscribers who do not accept cookies from the domain "LouisianaStateNewspapers.com" and associated web sites, may not be able to access certain areas of the web sites. For detailed information about our use of cookies see Frequently Asked Questions About Cookies in the Site Help area.
IP Addresses: LouisianaStateNewspapers.com logs IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We do not use IP address logs to track your session or your behavior on our site.
What does LouisianaStateNewspapers.com do with the information it gathers/tracks?Statistical Analysis and Banner Advertising: LouisianaStateNewspapers.com may perform statistical analyses of user behavior in order to measure interest in the various areas of our site (for product development purposes) and to inform advertisers as to how many consumers have seen or "clicked" their advertising banners. We also use demographic and preference information to allow advertising banners on our Web site to be targeted, in aggregate, to the users for whom they are most pertinent. This means that users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer's experience and the effectiveness of the ads. In this statistical analyses and banner advertisement targeting, we will disclose information to third parties only in aggregate form. Personal information about you as an individual subscriber will not be provided to any third party without your consent, except under the circumstances described in Compliance with Legal Process below.E-Mail: If you so elect, LouisianaStateNewspapers.com will periodically send you promotional email about services offered by LouisianaStateNewspapers.com and its advertisers. LouisianaStateNewspapers.com may contact you regarding account status, changes to the subscriber agreement, and to confirm registration. We will also send you other e-mails only if you have opted to subscribe to them. The E-Mail This Article feature is an easy way for LouisianaStateNewspapers.com to send articles through email. The e-mail addresses that you supply to use this service will not be used for any other purpose without your consent. LouisianaStateNewspapers.com does not send unsolicited e-mail.
We use e-mail links located in the Site Help area to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We will use your email address to respond directly to these questions or comments.Data Security: To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online.
With whom does LouisianaStateNewspapers.com share the information it gathers/tracks?LouisianaStateNewspapers.com shares the information it gathers, in aggregate form, with advertisers and other partners. We will not release personal information about you as an individual to third parties. We will not release personal information about you as an individual to third parties, except under the circumstances described in Compliance with Legal Process below.Forums: LouisianaStateNewspapers.com may offer Forums, or message boards. Any information you disclose when posting a message in these Forums becomes public. Moreover, subscribers who post a message in our Forums make their e-mail address available to others through a feature of our Forums software, which could result in unsolicited e-mail from other subscribers or parties.
Compliance with Legal ProcessWe may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of LouisianaStateNewspapers.com; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).
Opting-Out, Corrections and CancellationsUpon request, LouisianaStateNewspapers.com will a) Remove you and your personal information, from our database, thereby canceling your registration; b) Correct personal information that you state is erroneous; or c) Permit you to "opt out" of further e-mail contact (excepting notification of major changes to the service) while still allowing access to the site.
Read more: EuniceToday.com - The Eunice News | Eunice, La.
Already a Print Subscriber?
